With CS:GO gambling dying, I found out today that
you can use the gambling skins in a game called Counter-Strike: GO.
And for all you new players, I'm going to show you how to beat medium bots.
Although, I'm pretty bad at the game myself.
But I'm not that bad.
I lost, but it is my first time playing on medium,
I'm sure everyone loses on their first try.
I was wrong.
When I think about it now, back then I was naive.
The following days I was humiliated on every single CS:GO site.
In every language.
It even made international headlines.
I didn't know.. I didn't know how important it was to beat medium bots on your first try!
I was ready to give up...
...Move to Svalbard...
...Kill some polar bears.
But then I got an unexpected message from BOT Matt.
Leader of the medium bots.
BOT Matt: Your attempt was embarrassing.
BOT Matt: But to be honest, not one of us expected much.
BOT Matt: From a human.
BOT Matt: Bye bye, monkey!
KILIAN: I got insulted...
...By an expresso maker.
No... I wasn't going anywhere.
I was gonna train against easy bots.
For the next five years, every day I was gonna play fourty games.
It's...
It's more than it sounds.
At first, it was difficult.
I immediately understood that it would be impossible to play fourty games and sleep.
Therefore I had to quit sleeping.
Which was really good for my health, because sleeping is very addicting.
Another time consumer was prepearing meals, so I was only going to eat frosted flakes.
As it has everything needed for a complete breakfast.
The training almost killed me,
But after two months I noticed that when I had finished my fourty matches, the sun was still up.
So I added another twenty matches.
Then more matches.
Then, another hundred.
And then, even more matches.
After five years, I had played seven million matches.
It used to be just my mind playing, but now every atom that forms my body was playing CS:GO.
I could run at the speed of game sound,
Jump kilometers,
Triple wield shotguns,
Looking behind corners becomes useless when you have 4D vision!
And on hostage rescue maps, I could plant the bomb.
I was no longer just a CS:GO player,
I was a CS:GO god.
But all of this came with a price.
Because of my absence there was nothing stopping the medium bots.
And they had become esports superstars.
Completely undefeated, it was no longer about winning the tournaments,
It was about coming 2nd place.
And that made them famous.
So famous, they even got to meet the president.
Of Razer.
There is BOT Ethan, smartest robot on the planet and head of strategy.
Yet he doesn't solve equasions.
He scams kids online.
BOT Ethan: BOT ETHAN HAS DISCOVERED SITE.
010001101010011LOTTO.COM.
BOT ETHAN FUNCTION
IsOwnerOfWebsite = False;
KILIAN: There is BOT Irwing, and yes, as you can already tell, he's the handsome one.
And finally, of course, BOT Matt.
Programmed without empathy, and with only two things on his mind.
Complete and utter disdain for humanity.
And the opinion that Pluto is still a planet.
But they weren't world champions.
Dota had a real world championship, and now CS:GO was getting one too.
Valve called it: The Not Dota Tournament.
And the prize pool?
Ten million.
Iranian Rial.
It's about 320 dollars.
You also get a bag of pistachios.
So that's uh, pretty delicious.
The tournament was taking place three days after the announcement,
Making it impossible for any human pro to get a visa in time.
The tournament was rigged for the bots.
But before they were given the trophy, a new challenger appeared.
Me.
I walked from Sweden to Tehran.
It was fun, reached level 25 in Pokemon GO.
Welcome to the 2000-something Not Dota tournament!
Kilian VS The Medium Bots!
Who's gonna win?
They're playing so fast, I can't see them!
Why isn't Kilian buying anything?
Oh my god, he's not gonna rescue the hostages,
He's gonna pay the ransom!
The bots picked the Baby Marios, what?!
They are in space, ladies and gentlemen.
In space!
Only one round left.
Then all the bots died.
Someone put a magnet next to them.
All except BOT Matt.
His hatred made him immune to magnets.
And that's how IT works.
One final round.
Me VS BOT Matt.
1v1.
Man VS Machine.
Good VS Evil.
And that's...
...When I got banned!
.
So, Steam support, from your end it might've looked like I was cheating.
But I was actually standing up for humanity.
So you should unban me right now.
AND GIVE ME MY FUCKING PISTACHIOS!!!!!